<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>笔记 on Caleton Academy of Magic</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 笔记 on Caleton Academy of Magic</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>chiaralee953@foxmail.com (Caleton Academy of Magic)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>chiaralee953@foxmail.com (Caleton Academy of Magic)</webMaster>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>测试专用页</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/test-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>chiaralee953@foxmail.com (Caleton Academy of Magic)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/test-page/</guid>
      <description>1.Markdown 语法 元素 Markdown 语法 标题 (Heading) # H1 ## H2 ### H3 粗体 (Bold) bold text 斜体 (Italic) italicized text 引用块 (Blockquote) &amp;gt; blockquote 有序列表 (Ordered List) 1. First item 2. Second item 3. Third item 无序列表 (Unordered List) - First item - Second item - Third item 代码 (Code) code 分隔线 (Horizontal Rule) &amp;mdash; 链接 (Link) title 一级列表项 1 二级列表项 1.1 三级列表项 1.1.1 二级列表项 1.2 一级列表项 2 元素 Markdown 语法 表格 (Table) | Syntax | Description | | &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash; | &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash; | | Header | Title | | Paragraph | Text | 代码块 (Fenced Code Block) &amp;lt;br&amp;gt; { &amp;lt;br&amp;gt; &amp;quot;firstName&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;John&amp;quot;, &amp;lt;br&amp;gt; &amp;quot;lastName&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;Smith&amp;quot;, &amp;lt;br&amp;gt; &amp;quot;age&amp;quot;: 25 &amp;lt;br&amp;gt; } &amp;lt;br&amp;gt; 脚注 (Footnote) Here&amp;rsquo;s a sentence with a footnote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our Manufacturing Process Part III</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/process-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>chiaralee953@foxmail.com (Caleton Academy of Magic)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/process-3/</guid>
      <description>Machining is any process in which a cutting tool is used to remove small chips of material from the workpiece (the workpiece is often called the &amp;ldquo;work&amp;rdquo;). To perform the operation, relative motion is required between the tool and the work. This relative motion is achieved in most machining operation by means of a primary motion, called &amp;ldquo;cutting speed&amp;rdquo; and a secondary motion called &amp;ldquo;feed&amp;rdquo;.[7] The shape of the tool and its penetration into the work surface, combined with these motions, produce the desired shape of the resulting work surface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our Manufacturing Process Part II</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/process-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>chiaralee953@foxmail.com (Caleton Academy of Magic)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/process-2/</guid>
      <description>The three principal machining processes are classified as turning, drilling and milling. Other operations falling into miscellaneous categories include shaping, planing, boring, broaching and sawing.[5]&#xA;Turning operations are operations that rotate the workpiece as the primary method of moving metal against the cutting tool. Lathes are the principal machine tool used in turning. Milling operations are operations in which the cutting tool rotates to bring cutting edges to bear against the workpiece.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our Manufacturing Process Part I</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/process-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>chiaralee953@foxmail.com (Caleton Academy of Magic)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/process-1/</guid>
      <description>Machining is any of various processes in which a piece of raw material is cut into a desired final shape and size by a controlled material-removal process. The processes that have this common theme, controlled material removal, are today collectively known as subtractive manufacturing,[1] in distinction from processes of controlled material addition, which are known as additive manufacturing. Exactly what the &amp;ldquo;controlled&amp;rdquo; part of the definition implies can vary, but it almost always implies the use of machine tools (in addition to just power tools and hand tools).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Squares</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/building-squares/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>chiaralee953@foxmail.com (Caleton Academy of Magic)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/building-squares/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In geometry, a square is a regular quadrilateral, which means that it has four equal sides and four equal angles (90-degree angles, or (100-gradian angles or right angles). It can also be defined as a rectangle in which two adjacent sides have equal length. A square with vertices ABCD would be denoted ◻ ABCD.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical triangles</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/tropical-triangles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>chiaralee953@foxmail.com (Caleton Academy of Magic)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/tropical-triangles/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A triangle is a polygon with three edges and three vertices. It is one of the basic shapes in geometry. A triangle with vertices A, B, and C is denoted △ ABC.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
